喔  嘿  试镜如何
Oh, hey! How was your audition?
对不起  我认识你们吗
I'm sorry, do I know you?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
没事  我在练习假装不认识你们  因为我就要成为一个电影明星了
Nothing, I'm just Practicing blowing you off. because I'm gonna be a big movie star!
你得到那个角色了
Oh, you got it?
还没  但试镜很成功  什么样的角色
Well, no not yet, but the audition went really good. What's it for?
大成本制作  关于三个意大利兄弟
Oh, it's this big-budget period movie about three Italian brothers...
在世纪之初来到美国  是个真实经典故事
...who come to America around the turn of the century. It's really classy.
导演被认为是  下下个马丁史柯西斯
Oh, and the director is supposed to be the next-next Martin Scorsese.
"下下个"
The "next-next"?
来自芝加哥的那个家伙被认为是  下一个马丁史柯西斯
Yeah, there's this guy from Chicago who's supposed to be the next Martin Scorsese, all right?
这个导演在他之后
But then this guy's right after him.
喂
Hello?
乔伊  是伊斯特  刚和选角的谈过  他们很喜欢你
Joey, it's Estelle. I just talked to the casting people. They loved you!
他们很喜欢我
They loved me!
对  他们明天要再见你一次
Yeah, they want to see you again tomorrow.
我的天  只有一个问题
Oh, my God. There's just one thing.
你对正面全裸有问题吗
Do you have a problem with full-frontal nudity?
你开玩笑  我租过的电影都有正面全裸镜头
Are you kidding me? I never rent a movie without it!
哦
Oh.
好  我再回你电话
Uh, okay, let me call you back.
怎么回事  电影里需要我全裸
What's the matter? They want me to be totally naked in the movie!
哇  是啊
Wow. I know.
我祖母会看到的  祖母还得排队才看的到
My grandmother's gonna see this. Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
老友记  第七季  第19集   罗斯和摩妮卡的表妹
Friends  S07E19  The One With Ross and Monica's Cousin
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
婚礼就快到了  你紧张吗
Hey the Wedding's so close. Are you getting nervous?
紧张  不过我多少也有些盼着它赶紧结束
Yeah, but a part of me also can't wait 'til it's over.
钱德和我决定  婚礼前不做爱的
Chandler and I have this pact not to have sex again until the wedding.
"无性条约"  嗯
A "no sex" pact, huh?
我和全美每位女性  都有一份这个合约
I actually have one of those going on with every woman in America.
菲比  你能帮我整理客房吗
Hey Phoebe, will you give me a hand I gotta making up the guest bedroom?
表妹凯西要来和我们住几天
Hey, Cousin Cassie is coming to stay with us a few days.
凯西  我很久没看到她了
Cassie? Wow, I haven't seen her for like forever.
她是不是还带着芭比娃娃到处跑
I wonder if she still carries that a Barbie everywhere she goes.
罗斯  她25岁了  所以呢  我还是
Ross, she's 25 years old. So what! I still have--
哦  你大概是对的
No you're probably right.
嘿  嘿
Hi. Hey.
菲比  我能在这儿跟你谈点事吗
Pheebs, can I talk to you over here for a second?
好啊
Yeah.
狡猾的家伙
Subtle, guys.
什么
What?
我知道你们在计划  我告别单身女子的惊喜派对
I know you're planning my surprise bridal shower.
就算是吧  别破坏气氛  至少假装不知道啊
Ha, Well okay, Well don't ruin it! Just play along, at least.
好吧  对不起
Okay. Sorry. Okay.
天啊  我们还要替她办告别单身女子派对
Oh, my God. We have to throw her a shower?
嘿  那部影片你怎么决定的
Hey! What'd you decide to do about the movie?
我不知道
I don't know.
看起来不像个色情片  这是一个严肃  正统的电影  你知道
It's not like it's porn. This is a serious, legitimate movie. Y'know?
这个故事里的裸戏很重要
And the udity's really important to the story.
你也是这么说色情电影的
That's what you say about porn.
你说的对   也许我都不必回复他们
You're right. Maybe I shouldn't even go on the callback.
不  你应该去  很多大明星都演过裸戏
No, No you should. A lot of major actors do nude scenes.
我是说这是个当电影明星的机会  别错过啊
I mean the chance to star in a movie? Come on!
是真的  我只有一场裸戏  再说故事听起来真的很不错
Well that's true. And I'm only naked in one scene. Plus it sounds really great.
我的角色是个天主教徒   和一位犹太女孩恋爱了
My character's Catholic. He falls in love with a Jewish girl.
我们一起私奔  却陷在了大雨中
Who run away together and they get caught in this big rainstorm.
于是我们躲进谷仓  脱掉彼此的衣服  拥抱在一起
So we go into this barn, undress each other and hold each other.
真的很甜蜜而温柔
It's really sweet and tender.
那是啊  每个人都看到你那玩意了
Plus, everyone is gonna see your thing.
我们什么时候能开这个告别单身女子派对啊
Well when can we have this shower?
她有这么多事要做  我们只有两个选择
She has so much going on, we have only two options.
星期五  那只剩两天了
We have Friday. Well that's only two days away.
另外一个选择呢  昨天
What is the other option? Yesterday.
如果我们昨天就办了  问题解决了
Well, if we make it yesterday, woo-hoo, we're done.
天啊  菲比  这不可能  我们不可能在星期五办
Oh my God Phoebe, this is impossible! We can't do this by Friday.
要找地点  邀请客人  买好食物
We have to find a place, We have to invite people! get food.
太多事要做  不可能  办不到
There's just too much to do. It's impossible! We cannot do it!
办不到  瑞秋  镇静下来
We cannot do it! Rachel, Calm down!
好  抱歉  你是对的  你是对的  抱歉
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. you're right. I'm sorry.
镇静下来  女人
Just calm down, woman!
菲比  我已经  已经镇静下来了
Phoebe, I already. I already did.
那好  那我需要镇静
Oh okay. All right, then I need to calm down a little.
我认为如果组织得当  我们是能办成的
Okay. Okay. I think we can do this if we just get organized. All right?
有两天来计划这个派对
Uh-huh. We have two days to plan this party.
做决定要快
We just need to make fast decisions. Mm-hm.
好  要在哪里办
Okay? All right, where will we have it?
在这里  什么时间  4点整  食物
Um, here. What time? Four o'clock. Food?
小三明治和茶  好极了  好像摩妮卡
Finger sandwiches and tea. Ooh, great. Very Monica.
还有辣椒  这就太过头了
And chili. Ah, you went one too far.
花还是气球  两个都要
Uh, flowers or balloons? Both.
我们要付钱的  都不要
We're paying for this. Neither.
主题选什么呢  "肌肤之爱"
Um, what should we do for the theme? "Lusts of the Flesh."
什么  我不知道  牛仔主题怎么样
What? I don't know. Cowboy theme?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我很高兴我们决定婚礼前不上床
I'm really glad we decided not to sleep together before the wedding.
我也是
Oh, boy. Me too.
我在想  如果我们大吵一架
You know, I was thinking, if we had a big fight--
分手几个小时
Mm-hm. ...and, uh, we broke up for a few hours.
技术上来说  我们就可以上床了
Yeah. Technically, we could have sex again.
你说呢  专横独裁的家伙
What do you think, bossy and domineering?
婚礼取消了  肥胖幼稚的家伙
The Wedding's off, sloppy and immature.
我也正有此意  走吧
That's me. Come on. Okay.
等等  我们不能这么做  凯西在客房  我们要一起出去吃中餐
Okay. But wait. we can't. My Cousin Cassie is in the guest room. We're supposed to have lunch.
甩掉她  执拗尖锐的人
Well get rid of her, obsessive and shrill.
尖锐  婚礼照常
Shrill? The wedding is back on.
我听到有人讲话  你一定是钱德
I thought I heard voices. You must be Chandler.
嗨  很高兴认识你  很高兴认识你
Hi. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you too.
你准备好要走了吗   好了
So, are you ready to go? Yeah.
钱德  我跟你一起去
Chandler? I'll be right with you.
凯西必须去住你家  为什么
Cassie needs to stay at your place. What-Why?
因为这位 "变态人"   一直盯着她看
Because "Pervie Perverson" over here can't stop staring at her.
什么  钱德  她是我们的表妹
What?! Chandler, she's our cousin!
我没有盯着她看  我只是在专心倾听
I wasn't staring at her. Okay? I was just listening intently.
做一位好的聊天者  看着我
It's called being a good conversationalist. Watch.
说话
Say something.
你看着南面8英寸以外的地方
You were staring about eight inches south of there.
好吧  她可以来我家住
Fine. She can stay at my place.
顺便问下  凯西现在长成什么样子了
By the way, what-what does Cassie even look like now?
就像玛丽莲阿姨
She looks exactly like Aunt Marilyn. Huh.
玛丽莲阿姨会来参加婚礼吗
So this Aunt Marilyn, is she coming to the wedding?
别惹我发火
Wafer-thin ice.
嘿  我回来了
Hey, I'm back.
嗨  乔伊
Hi, Joey.
那我要不要再演一遍那场戏啊
Uh, so, will I be reading the same scene again?
其实  我们本来要打电话给你  你今天不用来这儿
Actually, I tried to call you. You didn't need to come today.
太好了
Oh, great.
我会是这个角色的最佳人选  不过随你便
Y'know I'd have been perfect for this part. but whatever!
谢谢你们做了个错误的决定  这会毁了你们的电影  再见
Y'know, thanks for making a bad decision and ruined your movie. Good day!
等等  乔伊  你不需要来这儿  因为导演昨天看了你的带子非常喜欢
Wait Joey! You didn't need to come down because the director saw your tape from yesterday and loved it.
下台鞠躬
And scene.
呀  很好玩吧
Huh? Wasn't that fun?
即席表演
We did a little improv there. Yeah!
你刚才在说
So, you-You were saying?
导演们认为你很适合  明天想见你
Well, the director thinks you're really right for the part and wants to meet you tomorrow.
哇  当然  太好了
Wow. Sure. That's great.
你的经纪人说你对裸戏没问题
Oh and your agent said you're okay with the nudity.
对  没错  只要是看着很有格调
Yeah! Yeah, sure. just long as it's handled tastefully.
而且谷仓里不要太冷就行
And that barn is not too cold.
好极了  还有一件事
Terrific. Well, uh, there's one more thing.
导演希望电影里  每一样东西都看上去真实可信
Uh... Uh, it's really important to the director that everything in this movie is authentic.
所以你和莎拉的性爱场面
Yeah and so in your love scene with Sarah...
她说她从没见过  非犹太人的裸体男子
...she talks about how she's never seen a naked man who wasn't Jewish.
所以
So...
所以怎样
So, what?
导演坚持演出这个角色的人
So, uh, well, the director is insisting that whoever play that part...
必须是从解剖学角度上来看
...be authentically, uh, anatomically...
不是个犹太人  你知道我在说什么
...not Jewish. You know what I'm saying?
知道
Yes!
不知道  你说什么
No. What?
在那时的意大利  一个天主教移民应该没有
An Italian Catholic immigrant at this time would not be...
割包皮
Bar mitzvah-ed?
那么说要得到这个角色  你就不能割过那个  对
So to get this part you can't be-Nope.
可你其实割了  对
But you are? Yep.
但你告诉他们  你没有割过  对
But you told them you weren't? That's right.
哇啊  哇啊
Wow. Wow.
那这就全完了  没有什么可努力的余地了
And it's definitely all gone? There's nothing there to work with?
你在想什么  我不知道  我想得到这个角色
What were you thinking? I don't know. I really want this part.
而且他们说不管试镜时问什么  都回答是
And they tell you no matter what you get asked at an audition you say yes.
如果要你骑马  你就说会骑
Like if-if they want you to ride a horse, you tell 'em you can
回头再去学
And just figure out how to do it later.
乔伊  这和学会骑马不一样  这就像是学习如何
Joey! This is not like learning to ride a horse. This is like learning to...
让衣服自己长出衣领来
...grow a turtleneck.
我知道  我知道  行了吗  明天我去见导演时
I know, I know! okay? And apparently tomorrow, when I go in to meet the director...
必须脱掉衣服  让他们检查我的身子
...I have to take off my clothes so  that they can see what my body looks like.
我的天  那你怎么办啊
Oh, my God. What are you gonna do?
看来我必须打给我的经纪人  告诉她我没法演
I just have to call my agent and tell her I can't do the part.
除非
Unless...
除非什么
Unless what?
这听起来可能有些疯狂  不过我们也许可以做点
Well, this may sound crazy, but there may be something we could...
造型
...fashion.
像什么  我还没想好  不过  嗯
Like what? Well, I'm not sure yet, but, um...
我突然有个念头  我在想
...off the top of my head, I'm thinking...
用双面胶和某一些午餐肉来做
...double-sided tape and some sort of luncheon meat.
嘿  我有个派对主题的好点子了
Hey! I've got a great idea for party favors for the shower. Okay,
我们找点桃木盒子  刻上每个人的名字
we get some uh mahogany boxes and carve everyone's names in them.
在里面放着每个人的出生石
and inside is everyone's individual birth stone.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
好吧  那你负责这个
All right, you take care of that. Okay.
还有  派对就在明天  我们还没有宾客名单
And meanwhile, the party's tomorrow and we still don't have a guest list.
好  好吧  我们知道谁会来  有我  你要来吗
Okay. Okay! Well okay, Who do we know that's coming? Me. Are you?
嘿  怎么样啊
Hey. Hey, what's up Mon?
我在替乔伊弄点东西  可以搜一下你的冰箱吗
Well uh, I'm trying to making something for Joey. Do you mind if I raid your fridge?
请便
Have at it.
好  火鸡肉  没用
Okay. All right. Turkey? Mm, that won't work.
起司  没用
Cheese? That won't work.
橄榄面包  希望这没用
Olive loaf? I hope that won't work.
你在替他做三明治吗
Are you making him a sandwich?
不  像是鸡肉卷
No, it's, um, more like a wrap.
好  我要走了
Okay, so, um, I'm gonna go, guys.
你们可以继续讨论  要送我什么礼物
I guess you can get back to deciding on what to get me for a present!
我们要送她礼物
We have to get her a present?
好吧  看我拿到什么
Okay, but look. Look at what I got.
她的通讯录  我们有宾客名单了
It's her address book. We have a guest list.
天啊  你好厉害  你从她皮包里拿的
Oh my God you're amazing. Did you pull that out of her purse?
嗯  还有一点派对的启动资金
Uh-huh. And a little seed money for the party.
凯西
Cassie?
嘿  罗斯  嘿
Hey, Ross. Hi. ha, ha.
好久不见
It's been so long!
上一次我看到你时
Last time I saw you...
你正忙着收帐篷好去看绝地武士
...you were setting up your tent in line to see Return of the Jedi.
对  没错
Oh, Oh, uh, that's right.
这么说你那天看见我了  我还以为你没看见呢
So-so you did see me that day. Because it seemed like you didn't.
对不起  没关系  来来  请进
Yeah, sorry about that. It's okay. Come, come on in.
谢谢你让我住在这儿  我是说摩妮卡那儿也不错
Thanks for letting me stay here. I mean Monica's place was nice.
只是她的未婚夫老是盯着我看
But her fiancee sure stares a lot.
我的天  你学钱德学得真像
Oh, my God! You do a great Chandler!
我很会模仿别人表情的
Uh-huh. Yeah, I have a knack for impressions.
也许等我们熟一点  你也可以学我
Well, maybe after we get re-acquainted, uh, you could do me.
好  不
Yeah. No!
凯西  你的 你的好吃吗
Cassie, how you--? How you doing on that...
热狗
hot dog.
我吃完了  感谢上帝
I'm all done. Thank God.
我记得我们最后一次见面  是我们父母一起租下那栋海滨别墅
I guess the last time we really hung out was when our parents rented that beach house together.
哦  对  没错  记得那时
Oh, right, right. Ooh, remember the time...
我把你按倒在地   搔你痒把你咯吱哭了
...l, uh, pinned you down and tickled you until you cried?
我们现在大了  不能那么做了
We're probably too old to do that now.
我一直都记得那个夏天  我就是那时长了这些雀斑的
I'll always remember that summer. because it's when I got all of these freckles.
嗯哼  还有  我也一直都记得那个夏天
Uh-huh! Uh-huh! And-And I'll always remember that summer...
因为那时我才意识到我们是亲戚
...because that's when I realized that we are related.
你长那么大才明白过来啊
It took you that long to figure it out, huh?
我是有点反应慢了
Well I'm, I'm a little slow.
就像我们的孩子也可能会这样子
Just as our children would be.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
你好吗  好  嗨  谢谢大家能来
How are you? Good. Hi. Thanks for coming.
谢谢  很高兴见到你
Oh, thank you. Thank you. No? All right. Oh, it's so nice to see you.
不  谢谢  好  瑞秋
No, thanks. Okay. Hey, Rash?
是  这些是什么人啊
Yeah? Who the hell are all these people?
我不知道  我打给摩尼卡本子里的每一个人
I don't know. I called all the people in Monica's phone book
这些都是通知到能在24小时内赶来的
and these are the only ones who could show up on 24 hours notice.
你知道有另一个词来形容这些人吗  输家
Hmm, y'know there's another word for people like that: Losers.
嗨  我是瑞秋  这是菲比  我是伴娘
Hi, I'm Rachel. This is Phoebe. I'm the maid of honor.
你怎么认识摩妮卡的
How do you know Monica?
我是她四年前的会计师
I was her accountant four years ago. Oh...
我很想知道  这过去四年是谁替她报税的
I'm very interested to find out who's been doing her taxes the last four years.
很好
That's great.
摩妮卡何时会到  我不知道
So, what time is Monica supposed to get here? I don't know.
请稍等片刻
Excuse us for a minute.
你没通知她来  是该你通知她的
You didn't tell her to come?! You were supposed to tell her!
不  不该我  是你该通知她来的  而我负责带蛋糕
No I wasn't! You were supposed to tell her to come! I was supposed to bringing the cake!
好  我打电话给她  对  然后要她带蛋糕来
Fine, I'll go call her. Yes! And please tell her to bring a cake!
好  我们有很多选择  有几个模型你可以试戴
Okay, we have a lot of options here, A number of prototypes for you to try on.
哇  看起来很棒
Wow, those look great.
对  这个蘑菇的伞做的头  这个是用意大利香肠做的
Yeah! Okay, this one's a mushroom cap. Uh, this one is made of bologna.
还有  还有牙签  只是撑着等胶水干掉
And-And the toothpicks? Oh, just until the glue dries.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
这些比较逼真  不过容易腐烂
Now, these are-are more realistic, but perishable.
这儿  粉红色的山羊皮  很不错
Okay? Over here, we have pink suede, which is nice.
不过  湿了就会缩水
But umm, if it gets wet, then you know it'll shrink.
把这个拿走好了
Well maybe we'll just take that one away.
我也做了一个有毛的  不过那是给我自己的
I also did a little something in fur, but, uh, that's really just for me.
那么  你干吗不进屋去试试这些玩意  我们就知道哪些有用
Okay. So, why don't you go into your room and try these on? We'll get a better idea of what's gonna work.
谢谢  你真是位好朋友  这事太诡异了
Thanks, you are such a good friend. And this is so weird.
牙签  对
Toothpick? Yeah.
你现在在试那个  水果卷
What are you trying now? The Fruit Roll-up.
怎么样  很好吃
And? Delicious.
乔伊
Joey.
等一下  等一下  有个合适的
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We have a winner!
什么  哪一个
What? Which one?
泥彩蛋  现在没那么傻了
The Silly Putty. It's not so silly anymore!
她是你表妹  她是你表妹
She's your cousin. She's your cousin.
如果她知道你脑袋里在想什么  她会以为你有病
If she knew what was going on in your head, she'd think you were sick.
她会吗  让我们回顾一下
Or would she? Let's back up for a second.
是她提议开红酒的
She was the one who suggested opening a bottle of wine.
是她把灯光调暗的
She was the one who turned down the lights.
是她要租《二十三世纪大逃亡》的
She was the one that wanted to rent Logan's Run...
有史以来最性感的电影
...the sexiest movie ever.
我知道这眼神
Oh, I know that look.
不管了  我想要  她想要
Forget it. I want it. She wants it.
我要行动了
I'm going in.
你在干什么
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
说点机智的
Say something clever.
好吧  不必机智的
Okay, doesn't have to be clever.
只要说点什么  说话
it just has to be words. Say some words.
什么话都好
Any words will do.
我的天  这是有史以来
Oh, my God, this is the longest...
最长的沉默
...that anyone has not talked ever!
说什么都比这样强啊
There is nothing you can say to make this worse...
说就是了
...so just say something!
我很久没做爱了
I haven't had sex in a very long time.
还不如不说话的好
Yeah, you really shouldn't have said anything.
菲比  瑞秋  是摩妮卡
Phoebe? Rachel? It's Monica.
什么事这么急着找我来呢
I wonder what you could possibly need me for on such short notice?
喔
Oh.
摩妮卡  我们很抱歉  为什么
Oh, Monica. We are so sorry. For what?
第一   忘了替你办告别单身女子派对
Well first, for forgetting to throw you a bridal shower.
而且还忘了邀请你
And then for forgetting to invite you to it.
你们已经办完了
You already had it?
我们打电话给你通讯录里每一个人  来了很多人
Yeah. Well, we called everyone in your phone book. A bunch of people came.
找你花了好久的时间  客人都走了
but it took us so long to get you here that they had to leave.
是啊  我们本想给你一个大惊喜  替你办一个大的告别单身女子派对
Yeah, we wanted to throw you a big surprise and a great shower.
现在两个都没了
and now you don't have either.
我们全搞砸了
We ruined everything. Ugh.
不  等一下  没有搞砸  你们做的非常好
Well no, wait a minute, that's not true. No, what did, that was really sweet.
其实这样子最好  什么意思
And it kind of works out for the best, heh. What do you mean?
我现在要和我真正喜欢的人一起共渡我的告别单身女子派对
Well now, I get to spend my shower with the only people I really love.
我是说  我收了所有的礼物  而不必和我不喜欢的人说话
I mean, I get all those presents without talking to people I don't even like!
惊喜  惊喜  摩妮卡
Surprise. Surprise, Monica.
最酷的是  这个角色是从尼泊尔来的
And what's cool is, the character is from Naples, right?
我全家都是从尼泊尔来的
Yeah. My whole family's from Naples.
太好了  我听得差不多了
Oh that's great. Okay. well I've heard everything I need to hear...
我们只需要
We just need to, uh...
莱斯莉
Leslie?
乔伊  这有点怪怪的  是  没有问题
Uh, Joey, this is the awkward part. Oh, hey, right. Not a problem.
我完全了解
I totally understand you need to...
你们需要知道我没有什么吓人的疤痕或纹身
...y'know make sure I don't have any horrible scars or tattoos.
不用担心
Don't you worry.
我没什么可隐瞒的
I have nothing to hide.
看这儿  这就是我的
So, there you go. That's me.
百分之百纯天然的
One hundred-percent natural.
我跟你们说  这事以前从没发生过
I tell you, that has never happened before.
凯西  在这儿都还好吗
Cassie, are you finding everything okay in there?
谢谢你让我住这儿
Yeah. Thank you so much for letting me stay here.
没问题  喔
Oh, it's no problem. I've...
怎么了
What?
说话啊  随便说点什么
Say something. Say anything.
约她出去  她又不是你表妹
Ask her out! She's not your cousin!